Fixed & Synced by bozxphd.Enjoy The Flick
Good morning, Raj sir.
- Good morning, Raj sir.
- Good morning.
Where's Veer?
He's taken Jerry's
car out for test-drive.
Okay. Good. Good.
Hi, good morning, Raj.
Good morning, Raj.
Raj...
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
It's been 15 years since
that incident occurred, Raj.
Oh, God. Save me.
Spare me... Don't beat me.
Hey...
Listen to me.
What are you all doing?
Stop.
Why are you all beating him?
Stop, please. Why are you beating him?
Raj, he stole Mr. Almeda's
cellphone and was trying to flee.
Why do you do such humiliating
things in the first place?
Whatever I have done,
is not my choice.
It's my helplessness.
What helplessness?
- Alcohol... or gambling?
- Shakti!
Let him speak.
I admit that I stole from him...
But it's not for me.
I did it for my younger brother.
- For your brother?
- Yes.
After my parents died...
he became entirely my responsibility.
I take care of him by stealing.
Why do you steal... to
take care of your brother?
You should do some work.
I am not educated.
A good-for-nothing loser.
What else can I do other
than steal from people?
Come and take a peak in my home.
I've a house,
but no money to pay rent.
There's a bulb, but no electricity.
Please... don't cry.
Shakti, give me your wallet please.
Please relax.
I...
Here.
- Keep this money.
- No...
No, Actually, keep all of it.
In case you need more,
then that's my house.
You can come anytime.
You're giving money to this Mani.
- But I stole...
- For your brother!
And when it's about your brother...
one thinks from the heart,
and not mind.
Veer... what are you doing?
If anything happens to the car
before delivering it to Jerry, then...
Raj and Shakti will skin us alive.
Chill, Siddhu.
I worked really hard
to modify this car.
I won't let a single scratch on it.
Enjoy the ride boy.
She's coming this way.
- I think she needs a lift.
- You're not offering a lift to that girl.
Why? - You know what
brother always says.
- What?
- Girls spell trouble.
- She's standing there all alone.
- I'm calling him up.
- Don't be crazy...
- Are you driving or should I call him?
Fine, I'm going.
Lift.
That was a really nice
and tall girl you made me miss.
Just keep driving quietly.
- Brothers bootlicker.
- What?
What now, Veer?
- I need to pee.
- Pee? What?
Come along and give me some company.
This is not some couple-dance.
And I don't need to do it.
You'll feel like doing it while
after watching and hearing me do it.
Come on.
- Now?
- Not yet.
- Not yet!
- Now?
- Yeah....
- Well, not me.
- Veer. Veer.
Concentrate on your peeing,
someone might see you.
Veer... where are you going?
Bye.
Veer!
- Hi.
- lshita.
- Veer! Can I help you?
Actually, my scooter broke-down!
- Oh no.
- I was heading to the Municipal Office.
You see, I am from Bangalore.
And I need to submit these papers...
in order to open
a restaurant in Panjim.
And today's the last day.
The office will close
down in 10 minutes.
- Can you please give me a lift?
- Let me hold you first.
- Huh?
- I mean the car-door...
so I can open it for you.
Please come.
Oh, God! Traffic!
What now?
Don't worry!
Watch out!
Thank God it's open.
Veer, you just made my day!
Thank you so much!
It's okay, it was my duty.
- Bye.
- Bye!
- Hello.
- Veer.
- Yes, brother.
- Jerry had called.
- Where is his car?
- Yes...
- And is everything okay?
- Yes, the car's...
Is fine!
Look, Raj... if Veer was fast...
doesn't mean you should get furious.
Cool it, Raj.
Chill, Raj.
Cool down, Raj?
Should I go cozy-up in the fridge now?
How did this happen?
What was the reason?
- Brother, I...
- Pee.
Pee?
He said he needs to pee...
and I should give him company.
As soon I started
peeing... he ran off. - Where?
I guess he went looking
for an open space.
Raj, peeing out in
the open is too much fun.
Disgusting Anwar...
Please don't discuss
your personal habits here.
How did this happen, Veer?
Brother, all this happened...
because I was trying
to help a helpless girl.
- Helpless girl?
- Yes.
Poor girl had to get
to the Corporation Office.
She had a deadline to meet
I gave her a lift, and in a haste...
And brother, you always taught me...
l should always be good,
even with the bad.
Sol...
And if it concerns a girl, then...
even if you've to smash the car,
but still...
you must go out
of your way to help her.
No, no...
- What are you laughing at?
- But I was only peeing.
That's all he's capable for.
Brother Shakti...
Pee
Tavde... get the screwdriver.
Yeah.
Can I leave?
I've to take my girlfriend for dinner.
Fine, go... but don't
wear shorts on your date.
Thank you.
- Pintu. I can't seem to open this.
- Can I go too?
Where do you have to go?
I am taking Tavde and
his girlfriend out to dinner.
- Fine, go.
- Thank you.
- Be on time tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
Veer.
- lshu.
- lshu?
- What are you doing here?
- Same old story.
My scooter breakdowns
more often than I can count.
- I'll check, I'm a professional.
- Okay
- lshu, it's got a serious issue.
- Really?
So now? - Do one thing
Give me your address.
I'll fix your scooter and
enter your house to deliver it.
Huh!
- Did you get your paperwork done?
- Oh that, yes!
Thanks to you.
- Are you a mechanic?
- Mechanic.
I am the owner of this place...
The whole and sole of this place.
But all this is because of you.
Because of me?
In order to drop you
at the Corporation Office...
this is what happened to the car.
And due to that... this
is what my brother has done to me.
Day and night... just work.
Oh I am So sorry!
I feel so bad for you Veer.
You feel for me?
Yeah... it's because of me.
Come here.
Sit here. Here!
- Who are you?
- Huh!
But yet... my heart wants to
share its personal feelings with you.
Go ahead, Veer.
Do you know what brother did...
after seeing the
car in this condition?
What did he do?
He slapped me 10 times
in front of everyone.
- Yes.
- How humiliating.
Didn't you stop him?
He's my elder brother.
I can't...
- It still pains.
- Let me see..
But I don't see any marks?
These are not exam papers
where you get to see marks.
Silly girl, it's on the inside.
You know what, lshu...
since the time I was a kid,
I loved studying.
But my brother... squandered
my entire education money...
on his girlfriend Uma Bai.
Why didn't you ever retaliate?
Confront him?
You should, Veer!
What "You Should"?
This woman's been provoking
me all the while. - Veer?
I won't hear another
wrong word against my brother.
- He's my elder brother.
- Yeah! Yeah!
You crazy woman!
She's mad!
- Really?
- I don't know her.
Oh... so he's your brother!
What kind of a brother are you?
You made him quit his studies.
And who hits his younger
brother like this.
Aren't you ashamed?
He won't tolerate this anymore.
Get that? - Okay.
Veer, come here.
- Don't be scared.
- No.
- Vent out all of your anger.
- Vent it out.
Come on, Veer... be your name.
Come on, Veer... be your name!
- Say it.
- Say it!
I...
Actually... he wants to say that...
his heart doesn't agree to this.
He wants you to leave.
If I fold my hands and apologies
in front of you. He won't like it.
After all, he's my younger brother.
But don't worry.
I'll apologies a lot to him.
- Fine.
- Thank you.
But you don't be scared.
If there's any problem, just call me.
- You have my number, don't you?
- You do, don't you?
Good... good...
Don't worry, he won't need it.
I am sorry. I am sorry, brother.
Who was the girl? You're always cooking up
stories after meeting a girl, aren't you?
- Come on. Let's go have dinner.
- No, brother.
I've sworn... l won't eat a
morsel until I don't fix this car.
No, Veer. You can't do that.
How can you stay hungry all night?
Don't be so hard on yourself, please.
Veer, here's your
double-chicken burger.
- Hi, brother.
- Hi.
- ls this yours?
- No!
You know... l can change
any car in this world...
But not you.
- Goodnight, brother.
- Goodnight.
Come on.
Brother took your burger.
Should I get more for you?
I've seen lshita,
I'm not hungry anymore.
Come on, Have this coffee now.
After all,
you've to stay awake all night.
- You're so concerned about me?
- Veer. I am your bro.
Okay?
Come on now, do your work properly.
And don't forget to drink your coffee.
Okay. Take care.
lshu... I am already missing you.
Oh my, God!
"O Girl... o Damsel."
"When I saw you move..."
"my heart raced ahead..."
"like a Olympic runner."
"Emotions evoked in my heart."
"My heart's move from its place."
"Shattered into pieces..."
"Like some gum you chew on."
"Emotions evoked in my heart."
"Beloved ...my traditional,
typical beloved."
"The cool shade in the scorching sun."
"l sway to the beat."
"Beloved."
"My beloved."
"My heart's stuck in a whirlpool."
"Hear me out in detail."
"I've lost everything in love."
"Tell me why my feelings..."
"means so low in your heart."
"Why didn't you show up...
after promising me?"
"The heart stayed up all night.."
"after this sweet betrayal."
"Emotions evoked in my heart."
"Beloved ...my traditional,
typical beloved."
"The cool shade in the scorching sun."
"l sway to the beat."
"Beloved ...my traditional,
typical beloved."
"The cool shade in the scorching sun."
"l sway to the beat."
"Beloved."
Good morning.
Veer... Son, take a look.
- Another robbery?
- Yes.
- The music system's gone.
- I fell asleep again.
- No!
It got stolen even though
you were on watch, son.
Exactly... who keeps
stealing at our place?
Oscar bhai.
Hi my cool... like an
empty swimming pool.
Come to your papa.
Here's your BMW 5 Series
Hi-fi music system.
That's more like it.
You know how to pull ropes...
Like Dominoes and Pizza Hut.
You get things so easily...
almost like you're
stealing from your own home.
There's no talent like you here,
Sony Moserbaer.
Oscar bhai... if you're
so impressed by my talent...
then how about you
give me some bonus.
You see... it's my girlfriend's birthday,
I want to impress her.
Of course... Of course...
Because today it's
also my sister's birthday.
Hello, Jenny.
Baby I've made arrangements
for the evening birthday party.
Wow! Wait, hold on.
- I'll ask my brother first.
- Yes, okay.
- Hello.
- Hello, brother.
Speak up my dear Laado...
Rolex, Rado.
My friends have arranged
a birthday party for me.
- Can I go with them?
- Of course, without a doubt.
Go live your life.
Here you go... Pampers, huggies.
- Hi.
- Hi, Veer.
- I've fixed your scooter.
- Oh, great.
Thanks.
- How much money do I owe you?
- What money?
You don't charge your kin.
- How sweet.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Goodnight.
Goodnight.
What's wrong, Veer?
Are you waiting for someone?
My friends were coming here
to pick me up.
I'd given them your address...
Wonder why they haven't arrived yet.
I don't know.
I'm sure they must be on their way.
By the way, if you want... we
can have coffee together.
- Together, what?
- Coffee!
Actually, Veer... l was thinking
about you before you got here.
What?
I mean... your brother.
How can he? Seriously Veer
I've never seen anyone so insensitive
and selfish like your brother.
How can any brother
be so heartless? - lshu.
- lshita, I lied to you.
- Lie.
My brother is not like
how I described him to you.
He loves me a lot.
More than you can imagine.
For me, I am always
first and then the rest.
Then why did you do all this?
Well...
When I saw you,
I wanted to talk to you.
After talking to you,
I wanted to be your friend.
You were giving me sympathy as well.
So I got carried away.
Veer.
You're crazy, you know.
What's up, guys.
This is my friend, Sid...
and that's his girlfriend... Jenny.
Hi.
- It's Jenny's birthday today.
- Oh... happy birthday.
Thank you.
lshita, I am sure you're
getting bored at home alone.
There must be a problem
with the cable as well...
and the internet speed's
must be slow too.
- Right?
- What?
What he really means to say
is... why don't you join us for dinner?
- Now, at this hour...
- And anyway.
You should never say
no to the birthday girl.
- Yeah!
- Come on.
Come on, lshita. It'll be fun.
Please come.
Come on.
Come on, lshita.
Okay, fine.
I'll just change and come.
I won't sell your drugs here.
Youngsters come here to have fun.
And I won't destroy their lives...
by selling them your drugs.
We work for King.
King. Get that.
Keep the stuff... and sell it.
You have to sell it!
Excuse me... this is not the way.
Let uncle go.
Don't interfere...
- Uncle Joe, you have to sell the stuff..
- Look here.
Let uncle go... or else
I'm calling the Police.
Oh my, God... you just murdered Her incoming
outgoing international communication device.
- What?
- Mobile!
Why did you break her mobile?
I just broke it.
Are you hurt?
Are you her boyfriend?
He's not my boyfriend... - Whether I am
or not, that's our personal matter.
We'll sort that out later. lshu.
Uncle Joe... what's the matter here?
They are King's men.
And they are telling me to sell drugs.
Drugs!
- Get lost. Come on.
- Leave!
Hey Hero... you don't
know what you've done today?
You just beat up King's men.
- King isn't going to spare you.
- Get lost.
What happened?
Beat him.
Die!
What's going on?
Hey...
Veer...
Who is that? Stop!
Stop them.
Veer.
Veer. Are you okay?
Are you hurt? Who were they?
He's okay now,
you can take him home tomorrow.
Veer, take proper rest. Okay.
- Thanks, doctor.
- Thank you, doctor.
- Be honest, who were they?
- I don't know.
- Siddhu, do you know?
- I... I...
I don't know, brother.
Hey...
- does it pain?
- Not too much.
Brave boy.
Here you go,
maybe this will make you feel better.
Isn't this the phone you wanted?
- Yes, but how did you know?
- I know everything.
- Veer, are you okay?
- lshu.
She's a casual friend,
but formal hi-hello.
Isn't it lshu.
Hi, brother. lshita.
She's very strict,
she might get furious.
Be clear, lshita or... lshu.
Whatever your heart likes.
It's a good thing you're here,
or I would've come to you instead.
That day your phone broke.
This is a gift for you. New phone.
I got it for you.
But... how can I take this?
- l... really can't...
- Keep it.
He got it for you with a lot of love...
new phone.
And anyway... you'll need a
phone for your formal 'hi-hello'.
I insist, take it.
Thank you.
Hey... take care.
Take good care of yourself Please.
See you guys-
New phone.
We've found out...
where we can find them!
Oh no!
Hey... who's there?
Michael, take a look.
Hey, stop.
Hey... you don't know
who you just messed with?
When King finds out,
he won't spare you.
Then tell him my name.
Tell him Kaali had come.
How much did he take?
He took nothing, just burnt everything.
Burnt it?!
Who dared to burn King's stuff...
Who?!
I don't know, king.
His face was covered.
He just told us his name and left.
How long are you going
to take to tell me his name?
Kaali.
Kaali!
Who is Kaali.
King remember the boy from the garage
we beat up. He has a big brother.
It could be him.
How can it be him?
It can't be him.
Nothing wrong in checking.
Let's go take a look.
What is it?
What?
Hey...
Veer. Veer!
Veer, what's going on?
They are the same guys who beat me up.
Right then...
You beat them up, they beat you up.
- Scores settled. End of story.
- Now leave.
But... - Veer.
You know I don't like violence.
Siddhu, take Veer away from here.
And give me that stick.
Pintu-Tavde... get back to work, go.
I am really sorry.
- I am truly embarrassed...
- Very fair.
- That was amazing justice.
- No, sir... it's your greatness.
I am just a small-time car modifier.
A connoisseur of cars...
Like for your old
classic... re-modified beauty...
El Dorado 1969,
is very close to your heart.
Of course it is.
And it should be...
because your beloved
father gifted this to you.
You're amazing.
- Are you a car astrologer?
- No, sir.
It's just years of experience.
That's fine, but how did
you guess about the father bit?
- You're an amazing man.
- No, sir, you're the amazing guy.
You're the man, just look at you.
With a hat.
Your... your father
must be so proud of you.
No!
- He's dead.
- I'm so sorry.
- Are you okay?
- I am okay.
- Are you fine?
- Can I tell you something?
- Yes, of course.
I killed my father.
He was no school-teacher,
he was a Don like me.
But when I took over the business,
to increase our sales,
I started selling drugs.
My father said,
"NO! its against our principals."
Against our principals?!
Our business has no principals!
So I killed him.
Patrick! Joshua!
From now on all my cars
will get modified here.
From today Raj will rule on Kings cars.
Nice one .. Ain't it?
Put that gun away.
Put that gun away!
Are you scared of guns?
Everyone is scared.
But you don't need
to be scared anymore.
Because I am there...
For any problem, you call on King.
If he's Kaali... then I'm not king,
I am the Queen.
Let's go.
He was pointing a gun at
you and asking... "Are you scared"?
Since we've turned decent...
the entire world has turned rouge!
Kaali...
Malik sir, we tried our best.
But couldn't stop Kaali
from taking the gold container.
Raghav... are Randhir's
men getting better...
or our men getting useless?
There was a time when Randhir and I...
used to commit small time
robberies at the docks.
And now he's messing with me.
That tone in his voice... is
only because of Kali.
- Shakti.
- Yeah.
Have you checked the list
for the meeting we called tomorrow?
Yes, I did.
You need to Wrap this
and be careful, okay? And ..
You'll carry on, I'll join you.
And those two,
they need to be wrapped
and they are sold so just be careful.
Hi. Excuse me.
- Yes.
- I...
Yeah, that one.
I am really sorry that
you're so injured because of me.
No, no, it's okay.
I'll get well within few days.
I'll drop you in my car.
No, no, it's okay,
I'll catch the tram. - No, allow me.
- I'll drop you till there, please.
- Okay.
- I am so sorry.
- Its okay.
By the way,
who were those men after me?
What a nice weather?
Do you live in Bulgaria?
- Actually, my hobby is fishing.
- What?
You're answering my question
with some random answer...
and I am doing the same with you.
Okay, alright.
Who were they?
Gangsters.
Gangsters?
Actually,
they were from our rival gang.
What?
Have you heard about Randhir Bakshi?
That Indian Don... who settled down here?
Yes. I am his son.
What happened? Are you scared?
No... why should I be scared?
I didn't harm your
daddy don in anyway...
that you guys will come and kill me.
I mean... l am not scared.
Then why are you walking in
the opposite direction?
The trams this way. Come on.
Come...
What's your name?
- Meera.
- Nice.
Meera Dev Malik.
And yours.
Kaali.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
No, you did something...
What happened?
You look modern,
but your name's Kaali.
Oh come on, it's not that old also.
- Kaali is a good name.
- No offence, but...
l am sure your daddy
threatens like this...
"Swear on Kaali,
I won't spare you alive."
No?
No?.. no.
That's funny.
That's really funny.
Come. - That is funny, see.
Swear on Kaali.
By the way,
Meera... were you born in Bulgaria?
No... actually papa came here from India.
Artifacts were his hobby.
So he opened an art gallery.
And... even I do street-exhibitions
of my paintings.
- Yeah, I saw that.
- Ouch... l am so sorry.
I'm feeling really guilty
seeing you in this condition.
- You're feeling guilty!
- A lot.
- Then pay my hospital bills.
- What?
I'm hurt,
I had to buy crutches... and medicines...
You know how expensive they are?, Right?
So you just pay the money,
which will help me. - Okay.
No need to draw your gun for
such a small thing? - It's not a gun.
- It's my phone.
- Oh... Thank God.
Give me your number.
My number?
Yes, I mean... I'll call
your number from my number...
and then you'll have
my number on your number.
- Oh really..
- Yeah, really?
I mean... when you go to the hospital,
they will give you the bill.
So you'll have to call me and tell me.
Or is it No?
088743... 3... what?
- Come on, come on quickly.
- Brother.
Give me a five.
Yes!
What tall you've become.
Papa“.
- How are you Veer?
- I am fine.
Look at all the gifts we've got for you.
This means I'm not going
home this time either.
- No one loves me.
- Veer.
And brother,
you don't even remember me.
Veer... why are you including me?
Veer!
I'll go handle it.
Veer... Oye!
Dad's just...
What should I say?
You're absolutely right.
We only come meet you once in a month.
But... that's a different thing that
without you, every day seems like a month.
And also you're right,
I don't miss you at all.
But... that's a different thing that
that we only miss someone we can forget.
And you're absolutely right,
we don't take you home...
But... then it's a different thing that,
we're making a new home...
which will have a
huge room for little Veer.
Where You, me and Dad will
live in it together.
Really, brother?
I love you.
Bye.
What are you thinking, Dad?
Just that we can't let Veer
stay with us because of this enmity.
There's always threat to life...
and he's only a small kid.
But Kaali, if it wasn't for you...
l don't know how I
could've handled all this.
No, Dad.
Can I say something to you in a honesty?
Sometimes I wonder...
if I've been unfair to you.
You see... I'm educating Veer here.
But... l always kept you close to me.
Burdened you with the
responsibility of my work.
And always put your life in danger.
I mean... just because
you're not my blood...
l hope you don't misunderstand me.
No, dad.
Not at all.
I had no one.
You picked me up from the streets.
You want to know the truth, Dad.
Even you don't know this.
But you love me more than Veer.
Really!
Promise me, Kaali...
Veer should never know that
you two aren't blood brothers.
He'll never find out.
But promise me...
you'll never discuss blood ties again.
- Careful.
- Bye, Kaali.
I'll see you, dad.
Hello, Meera.
Actually,
Kaali, I called you here because...
there are some guys
who've been bothering me.
Good good.
Kaali.?
Kaali.!
- Are you listening?
- Yes, I am all ears.
Some guys have been troubling me.
They bother me.
And... l am the only Indian
Sketch artist in this area.
- So... they also pass racist comments.
- Really?
Yes.
Just tell me where I can find them.
Hey, Indian girl.
Did you sketch that one?
You wanna make a portrait of me.
I'll give you a kiss in return.
Come on, don't be shy.
What is your problem?
Get the hell out of here.
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
What happened to
all that attitude? Yeah!
Nothing to say? Huh!
And you... you wanted to kiss me, right.
Go ahead.
No.
No?
Who the man now?
Me the man.
Yeah... and you want to see
how the Indians do it? Huh?
Touch me.
Touch me. Just touch me.
Touch me now.
Just touch me.
Touch me... What?
They are gone.
They had to.
- Come on.
- Okay.
- I taught them a good lesson.
- Yeah, wow!
- Martina, just wrap up please.
- Bye Martina.
- And thanks to you too.
- No, no What did I do?
Meera, you were saying
about those hospital bills.
If you give them to me,
I'll pay for them.
No... don't worry about it.
- Today is your lucky day.
- Really, why?
You helped me out today.
So scores settled.
Wow! You're so fair.
- I must admit, Meera.
- You must. I agree.
Take today for instance,
I had to interfere after all.
Yeah, the way you interfered...
"Me the man." Me the man.
Very impressive.
It's important to
make them fear you. Yeah.
If only they had stayed a minute more,
I would've...
No, no, no, Meera. Forsake your anger.
You don't get it, Kaali.
You have to adapt to the worldly ways.
There's no point
in living like coward.
cowards are the ones who...
Oh my, God! Oh my, God!
- Don't move, Meera. Freeze.
- Why?
If you move,
he'll feel threatened and bite you.
Looks like a wolf.
But don't be scared.
Just be still. Breathe with me.
Breathe in.
Yeah. Breathe with me.
Bad doggie. Good Meera. Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Keep breathing. Nice.
Good Meera.
- Is he coming back?
- Who?
I think you scared the dog away too.
Just“.
Meera, I wanted to know...
can you have lunch with me today?
- I've to visit dad's art gallery today.
- No problem.
Dinner tomorrow?
Tomorrow... is mom and dad's anniversary.
Oh darn.
I mean good. Congratulations.
- Breakfast day after...
- Well, day after...
Don't say no.
All I need is five minutes.
- Five minutes?
- Only five.
Okay, done.
Give me five!
- Hi.
I thought you wouldn't come.
Thank you... thank you
so much that you came.
- So...
- So we've a date.
- You know we have only five minutes.
- Yeah, I know.
And your time starts now.
Okay, okay.
You're being really strict. Wait.
Come quickly. Come quickly.
- Your ride, ma'am.
- This?
Yeah... it's a bit far.
Yeah, don't ask questions. Hurry up.
Thank you very much Robert,
now hurry up.
Okay boss.
Restaurant.
- Restaurant?
- Yeah. It's a big date.
We'll start with food.
- You do know we've only five minutes.
- Yeah, I know. I heard it.
Tell me something, Meera.
You told me about your dad
and also how special he's for you.
ls there anyone else in
your life who's just as special?
- Are you trying to find out?
- I've found out.
You wouldn't have come on
this date if there was someone special.
And here we are. Let's go.
- Allow me, ma'am.
- Okay.
- And thank you very much, Robert.
- Welcome, boss.
Alright.
Meera, this is my favorite restaurant.
And this is the first
time I've brought someone here.
Please take a seat.
- Hi, boys.
- Hello.
You guys.
- Job change?
- They're multi-talented.
- Okay.
- So, what would you like to eat?
Arabian. Chinese.
French. Italian. English... - Chinese.
Chinese it is.
- Chinese.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
- Meera.
- Yeah.
- Did you make all those paintings?
- Yeah, you like them?
Love them,
I think they were beautiful.
Aaawww.
Actually, they were so beautiful...
that you can't take
your eyes off them.
I don't think you're talking
about paintings anymore.
Kaali.
Kaali!
Bill. You're Right.
Only four minutes left. Get the bill.
Your bill.
Shall I pay this bill just like
I offered to pay the hospital bill?
No, no, I'll pay it.
Will you take a cheque?
No cheque, only cash.
Here it is.
And don't waste time, quickly.
Welcome.
You've given me only five minutes.
Come on.
The meal was really nice,
but what about dessert?
- Dessert?
- Yeah, I want ice-cream.
- I want ice-cream.
- Okay, okay.
Ice-cream.
Fast.
Oh my, God.
We don't have much time, Robert.
Let's go quickly.
- Okay boss, okay.
- To my ice-cream parlor. Okay.
- Your... Your ice-cream parlor.
- It's my fathers.
Thank God... there's no traffic.
Otherwise we would've
been stuck for good.
- We're here, boss.
- We are here!
Oh lovely, We're here.
Come quickly.
Come into my ice-cream parlor...
said the spider to the fly.
Here we are.
- Job change again?
- He's multi-talented as well.
So what flavor would you like to have?
Vanilla. Butter-scotch. Strawberry.
- Belgium-chocolate chip.
- Who?
- Belgium-chocolate chip?
Thank God!
Although we came this far,
but you got your flavor.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
Thank you.
Oh, wow!
Belgium-chocolate... nice.
I am loving it.
Actually Kaali, seeing you like this...
it's hard to believe
you do such a dangerous job.
I know, I'm a pretty boy.
Aren't you scared?
I had no weakness before,
so I had no fear.
But now... l don't know.
- So... any other surprises?
- Of course.
It's not over yet.
Here you are. Thank you.
Flowers for my lady.
- Thank you, they're beautiful.
- It's alright.
- Anything else?
- No!
You gave me only five minutes,
so... date's over.
Damn!
- So I think you like me.
- Of course I like you.
I paid all the bills, in cash.
I must like you.
That's true.
So let's meet tomorrow?
I've an important job tomorrow.
We can meet day after. Please.
- But... it's my birthday tomorrow.
- I am so sorry, I didn't know.
But..
If you don't come,
I won't celebrate my birthday.
You see, Meera... I've to take
a consignment to Romania tomorrow.
Dad has spoken to the border police.
Everything's been set.
And we must deliver the
consignment to our buyers tomorrow.
- Please.
- Then I'll come along too.
We'll celebrate my
birthday on the border.
- Good idea.
- No! Bad idea.
Our rival Malik had his eyes...
on the gold consignment
I'm talking about.
You can say that I have snatched
this gold away from him.
And you don't know
Malik... he's a dangerous man.
Anything is possible. Over there.
You don't know how
dangerous it is out there.
Really.
You're not letting me come,
nor are you coming over.
This is not done.
I won't celebrate my birthday
without you, and that's it.
Okay, then... I'll finish
my job tomorrow at any condition...
and be back by tomorrow evening.
To you.
- Sure?
- Sure.
- Promise.
- Okay, yes.
Promise!
Kaali... we'll definitely meet tomorrow.
Bye.
"Never say goodbye."
"Always be mine,
never say goodbye."
Someone is following us.
Keep moving.
Hi.
What happened?
You look shocked...
like your entire
world turned upside-down.
Didn't I say... we'll
definitely meet today?
And what did you say?
"Don't come... it's dangerous."
Actually... the danger
you were talking about...
That danger is me.
You didn't get it.
Try to remember, Kaali.
What did I tell you my full name was?
Meera... Dev... Malik!
Malik!
My dad!
"The tone in his voice...
is because of Kaali."
And you know the best part...
it's my birthday, but...
I'll gift this gold to my dad.
Because... I'm one of
those big-hearted types.
That's why I planned all this.
What did you think?
You rammed me with your car?
No... l came in front myself.
So that my men could kill you.
But they missed.
And the things I had to do after that...
to get the gold's
information from you.
Pretended to be cripple...
I made my men pose as my enemies...
And I even went on
that stupid date with you.
God!
By the way... how was my acting?
World-class, right?
No!
I spare you...
It's my birthday.
- I won't spare that Malik now.
- No, dad.
You won't do anything.
I'm the one who's been betrayed...
- so I'll do what needs to be done.
- But...
Please, Dad.
I want to meet Meera once.
- Hello.
- Stop the car, Meera.
Meera, stop the car.
Stop the car, Meera.
Don't be scared.
I won't let go.
I have loved you with all my heart...
and didn't use my brains,
like you did.
Meera... after today don't ever
show me your face again.
I will kill you.
"Goodbye. ."
I am sorry.
I've been unfair to you.
Whereas to you... have only loved.
The thing you had faith on... was love.
But the only difference was...
that you realized it first.'
And I have realized it now.
You might not even believe me...
but I have to say this.
I love you!
Kaali!
Kaali, Listen to me
Kaali, I won't leave until
you don't believe me.
Please, Kaali.
Just believe me.
Please.
Kaali...
Kaali!
Would you like some dinner?
I see... you must be on a diet.
It's raining,
how about I get you some...
Coffee! Coffee!
It's okay...
- What do you want to prove?
- That I love you.
Why should I believe you?
You believed me when
I didn't love you.
And now that I do,
you don't believe me.
What's the problem?
I don't want to be betrayed again.
You can shoot me if I do.
Firing bullets...
using guns.. taking lives.
Isn't there anything else you can do?
I don't.
But you do.
You Teach me.
Please!
"Permeating through the sunlight."
"Slipping through the shades."
"When we met..."
"the moment froze."
"The sky melted."
"Converged into a glass."
"And froze into the
shape of your face."
"I've renounced the world..."
"to be with you."
"Just one prayer that
comes from my heart."
"Color me saffron."
"A prayer straight
from the beloved's heart."
"Color me saffron."
"A prayer straight from the heart."
"Starts with you..."
"and ends on you."
"This saga is eternal."
"l am the journey..."
"and you're the destination."
"Every path..."
"leads only to you."
"As my heart..."
"carefully united with yours."
"It alleviated the fog of my pain."
"I've renounced the world..."
"to be with you."
"Just one prayer that
comes from my heart."
"Color me saffron."
"A prayer straight
from the beloved's heart."
"Color me saffron."
"My world..."
"was completely lonely."
"But since the day you arrived..."
"Your arrival, gave life...
to my soulless body."
"All the relations in the world..."
"seem meaningless."
"My bond with you has deepened."
"I've renounced the world...
to be with you."
"Just one prayer that
comes from my heart."
"Color me saffron."
"A prayer straight
from the beloved's heart."
"Color me saffron."
"A prayer straight from the heart."
"Color me saffron"
Kaali.
We should tell our families about us.
I don't want them to
find out from somewhere else.
It won't be nice.
Yeah, you're right.
You know, I can convince my dad.
But what about your dad?
I hope he doesn't think that...
Me and my dad have cooked
up some plan to deceive him.
I will explain it to him.
And anyway, he doesn't hate you
as much as he loves me.
Yeah... l am sure.
But tell me one thing ...what if Me
and my dad have really made a plan?
So Then I will shoot you!
- Another robbery?
- Yeah.
- Imported headlights are gone too.
- I fell asleep again?
- Yes.
You're so consistent, Veer.
This car needs to be
delivered in the evening...
but we don't have headlights.
I wonder what's going to happen.
Don't worry, brother.
This is my fault.
I'll think of something.
Leave it to me.
Anwar, what are you doing?
Raj, he's is the thief.
Look at what he was stealing
and going with.
Mani, back to your old tricks again.
It's a cake.
That's what I've been trying
to tell you, that it's a cake!
Mani, you're stealing cakes now?
No, Raj, it's my happy birthday.
I bought this cake from his café.
Look, I even have the bill.
I thought I'll sit
with my brother Raj...
and we'll eat this cake together.
Just because a man is dark skinned
you will trash him so hard.
Sorry, Mani. Sorry.
Anwar, how could you
without seeing or thinking...
Mani, there's been a
theft in the garage again.
- So there's a bit of confusion.
- I see.
- Sorry.
- No, no not a problem.
- Come on... let it go..let's cut it.
- Who?
Your cake.
I got scared.
Anwar, get the candles.
Don't take it to your heart,
he's a bit emotional.
So he raised his hand on you.
Anwar.
You too Anwar.
Hey... why are you sulking?
Mani bhai, I need to arrange
for imported headlights.
Where do I get them from?
- Imported headlights?
- Yeah.
Don't worry.
There's only one
man you can get it from.
Oscar bhai.
Wow, Mani... you're so lucky...
Like Nokia, Blackberry.
My no. 1 thief just called.
He's getting the same
brand projector lamps...
like the one you wanted.
He said he stole it last night.
Do it fast, son.
See... this speaker and
That music-system... which are sold.
Look here.
This is a BMW Steering Wheel.
All this is his loot, Mani.
When will my...
I mean, your no.1 thief?
Wait for 5 minutes.
He must be on the way...
McDonald Subway. - Okay.
- We'll wait outside.
- Yeah.
It's the same thief who
robbed our entire garage.
- Let him come...
- Yeah, let him.
I'll tie a wrist
watch on both his arms.
What will that do?
Then he'll know his time's up.
He's got the same headlights.
- Oscar bhai...
- Yeah.
Here's comes my number one
'Chor' (THIEF).... Boxer, Labrador.
Keep it.
You are my ace of spades...
best in best.
Keep this... 30,000 Siddhu.
Go and squander all
of it on your girlfriend.
But tell me one thing.
Just like ATM spins out money,
how do you manage all this?
- Coffee.
- Coffee? Coffee
Oscar bhai, I've a friend.
And he trusts me more than required
I put sleeping pills
in his coffee, and...
Siddhu...!
Veer... what are you doing here?
Veer, listen to me...
Let's sit down and talk.
Rascal..
- Veer...
- Beat him.
Why are you running?
Stop!
Stop thief.
Don't let him go.
Veer. Veer.
Stop!
Veer...
Veer, listen to me.
Veer. Veer.
Hit him.
Hit him. Hit him.
How dare you touch Raj's stuff?
How dare you steal at Raj's place?
I'll cut off your hands.
Veer, enough. Enough!
Nagpada. Agripada...
He's down. He's fallen down.
Veer... Veer, we can discuss
this over a cup of coffee.
Coffee!
- To hell with your coffee...
- Enough! Enough Veer!
I took you as a brother not as a friend.
I would've tolerated it
If anyone else had done this.
But you did this to me.
Let's go, Mani.
What happened Veer?
I didn't ask you to stop...
then why did you stop?
You must have said 'stop' 50 times.
I just blurted that out in extempore.
How can a bus fit in a tempo.
- Extempore... Mani bhai.
- Was it a big tempo?
Mani... quiet!
Veer... you saw what your brother did.
And how.
But... you consider me a brother,
don't you?
You never bothered
to ask why I did it.
Look at me.
The same old shirt,
the same old jeans...
and the same old
shoes that you gave me.
I have never spent a penny on myself.
I have spent everything
on my love... my Jenny.
It wasn't easy to win her heart.
You rascal... look at your own fate.
We both grew up in a boy's hostel.
No sign or symbol of girls.
And when we came out...
we were surrounded
by a brother or an uncle...
We spent our entire youth amongst men!
It's true, Siddhu.
I went through so much trouble
to cajole that Monica aunty.
Aunty?
- The neighbor's maid.
- I see.
I was serious about her.
But before I could tell her...
she ran off with
that puncture-repairer.
Life's been so hard on us...
that we never got any girl in our life.
And see... l can't even
tell lshita... that I love her.
- Veer, why are you crying?
- You're crying too.
Your brother's still alive.
- I will help you.
- You will.
Yes... and you'll help me in return.
You won't tell our brothers...
that I was the one
who stole all that stuff.
Rascal...
Sorry, but you just wait and
watch the ideas I give you now.
You won't stay bachelor any more.
In fact, no one will
stay bachelor anymore.
We'll even find a Mani-ben
for this Mani-bhai.
Well said.
Even my parents never
thought about me, but you did.
You're not human, you're definitely
some angel. Get yourself checked up.
I am there.
Veer, just see what I do now.
Just wait and watch.
- What are you doing?
- What's this?
Where's Veer?
Why isn't he here yet?
Veer? Look!
He's waiting for you there.
Waiting for me?
- Hi.
lshita, I could never
muster the courage to say this.
But on this Christmas Eve...
l want to convey his message to you.
Whose?
My heart..
Go ahead.
Well, normally people celebrate
Christmas with someone special.
But they are all
dying to go out with me.
But I will only go...
with her!
I've lied to you many times.
But it's said that we should
speak only the truth on Christmas.
So the truth is I really...
I will be with you every
moment... for all my life.
Even if you look
like this years later.
Brother... please handle it.
Veer.
There's something I want to say.
Tell me.
I think we should tell
our families about us.
- What's the hurry, lshu?
- I mean we've just started now.
Veer...
I don't want them to
find out from someone else.
I won't like it.
We should talk to them.
Yeah.
What yeah...
I will talk to my family...
- Will you be able to tell your brother, or...
- lshu.
We love each other. It's not a crime.
I'll tell brother on his face...
It's been 28 minutes...
will you say something?
All you've been saying
is "l want to say something"...
What?
I want to share my
personal feelings with you.
Yeah.
- I need some time.
- Okay, okay, take your time.
I want to celebrate my
'Suhagraat' (WEDDING NIGHT).
With whom?
Su...
Subhash... I want to
tell you about Subhash.
He's bringing the bumper
tomorrow... at the garage.
You took 29 minutes to say that.
Don't worry, I'll collect
the bumper from Subhash, okay?
I want to marry you.
- What...
- No.
What are you saying?
I want to kiss you lip-to-lip.
Are you crazy?
What's he blabbering.
I'll tell you.
I knew he couldn't say it.
Actually, brother...
we really love each other.
- Really?
- Yes.
And I didn't want you to
find this out from someone else.
I wouldn't like it.
Raj... Veer isn't fooling
around this time..
He's found the right girl this time.
Yes, she's the right call-girl.
Oh Anwar...
- I am...
- Really sorry.
Actually I would like
to meet your family.
Let me know if they're free tomorrow.
- I'll come over.
- Okay.
Sir... madam will come
down in two minutes.
Would you like some tea or coffee?
No. This is fine, thank you.
Okay, sir.
I am sorry,
I think you are...
After coming to know
that you're Veer's brother...
l won't let lshita meet Veer again.
You were mistaken, Meera.
I wanted to tell you the truth.
But until then...
you were already gone.
You only broke my trust, Kaali.
I spared your life
today for lshita's sake.
But if you come back here again,
I will kill you.
- 'Dear...
- Yes.'
'Dear... you've managed to convince me.'
'But... l know your
stubborn father too well.'
'He will never agree
to this relationship.'
'I will convince him.'
Fine...
l am ready to meet them.
Thank you so much, dad.
I can tolerate anything...
but not your sad face.
Thank you.
Malik sir, what have you done?
You're going to bow down before
that Randhir for your daughter's sake.
You didn't get it, Raghav.
I can bow my head down
before my enemies for Meera...
but I cannot kneel in front of them.
It's time to end this enmity forever.
I've often seen and heard...
that years of friendship
one day turns into a relationship.
But Malik, this is the first time...
when an old enmity is
turning into a relationship.
There's another way
to end the enmity, Randhir.
Kill the enemy.
Where's Meera?
You see, Kaali...
Meera loves you a lot.
She couldn't have seen
you and your father die.
Meera... Kaali and his
father have deceived us.
They have attacked us.
Dad!
Try to understand, Meera.
Randhir Bakshi's men won't
stay quiet after what happened.
If not yourself,
then Think about lshita.
Think about how all this
will affect her when she finds out.
You're like a sister to me, Meera.
Listen to me.
Take lshita far away from here.
And start a new life.
We'll always protect you.
Meera has gone far away.
No one knows where.
But I want to see Meera at any cost.
I must tell her what happened there.
Kaali, I am not too intelligent.
But all this bloodshed
has taught me one thing.
There's no meaning to this life.
It's best if you forget
everything... and think about Veer.
Let's go together...
We'll start a new life. Right?
It's hard to believe...
that fate's repeating
the same story 15 years later.
Seems like we're back
to square one.
Yeah, Raj.
There are many other
Countries in the world...
other than India and Bulgaria.
But... they had to open
a hotel at this place.
All these years I
hid this truth from Veer...
and he shouldn't find out now either.
We must stop Veer at any cost.
And anyway... Meera...
Will never agree to this relation.
But I want to know...
what's the reason
behind your rejection.
It's a big one, that's it.
I do not want any more discussion
over this, lshu.
Forget him.
But why?
What happened between
lshita's sister and you...
that you said no.
I already told you...
you won't ask any more questions.
- There's some reason.
- Brother...
Veer! There's a reason.
- It's a serious matter.
- But what is the matter.
Look Sid, it's clear that...
Raj brother knows Meera, otherwise...
what can be the reason to say no.
- Who knows about your brother's past?
- brother knows.
The answer's correct...
but the direction is wrong.
the person who knows about
your brother's past...
is my brother!
Peter.
Feed him something special today
and don't charge him.
- Come on.
- I said I don't know.
Now go away,
I've a lot of customers to attend to.
Yogesh... are you going
to order something...
or take this TV home.
I'll place my order in five minutes.
You definitely know something.
You must tell me today.
What?
I won't budge until you don't tell me.
Brother Shakti, please say something.
Anwar brother... please
tell us their story.
No... Anwar brother, for my sake...
please tell us.
Don't do this.
Their story?
- They were thieves.
- Anwar!
- Thieves?
Anwar!
He means... they stole
each other's heart.
Raj and Meera had an affair.
Brother, please tell
us from the beginning. - Yes.
Your brother's real
name was never Raj. - Anwar!
He means... his real name was...
Ramlal.
- Ramlal!
- Ramlal?
And he loved bashing...
He means he loved cleaning clothes.
- Why?
- Because Ramlal was a washerman.
Brother was a washerman.
Then lshita's sister
must have a real name too.
lshita's sister's real name...
- Pogo!
- Pogo?
Ramlal and Pogo...
- How did they meet?
- Meet... how?
One day Pogo was walking all alone...
when some goons came after her.
That's when Ramlal
slammed them to the ground.
- How can brother slam anyone...
- He was a washerman...
So he slammed them on the ground.
Then? - Then Pogo met
him every morning for tea.
- Then?
- Then“.
They would meet in
the evening in toilets.
Why the toilet?
- Hand pump.
- Yeah.
Because Ramlal would wash his clothes...
at the hand pump which
was below Pogo's toilet.
If their love was so pumped up...
then how did it turn into hatred?
Hatred...
Gold is my God.
Pogo loved diamonds,
jewels, gold and silver.
Their love story was somewhat like...
'Khana Khazana' (COOKERY SHOW).
'Khana Khazana'...
what are you saying?
Because Ramlal could
barely manage a square meal...
and Pogo was looking for treasure.
Then? - And one day...
tired of all the arguments...
your brother turned
into a... 'Chakka' (EUNUCH).
Brother turned into a...
'Chakka' (EUNUCH)...How's this?
He means to say...
Yes, brother turned
into a... 'Chakka' (EUNUCH).
brother turned into
a... 'Chakka' (EUNUCH) again.
- Veer, this is why he never got married.
- You shut up.
I mean Ramlal was devastated...
because he couldn't
fulfill Pogo's demands.
And in between those two...
'Daraar' (VOID).
'Judaai' (SEPARATION).
'Dushmani' (ENMITY).
'Tashan' (STYLE).
Oh my, God.
- "Oh my, God" In between them?
- It's just an expression.
Don't people say "Oh my,
God" when someone separates.
Peter... cut-off that customer's finger.
Who keeps pressing
the remote so frequently?
Brother Shakti, I remember...
when dad and brother used
to come meet me at the hostel...
they always wore good clothes...
and came in big cars, we were rich.
Because your brother was a washerman.
He used to wear his
customer's clothes.
And your dad was a mechanic.
He would drive his customer's car.
Just like you do.
You're a mechanic as well.
Go and fix cars... go on!
Go!
Brother...
Was our father a waiter or...
You get lost to... come on, get out.
Such an emotional story.
This is wrong.
- Anwar brother...
Who asked you to open your mouth?
Shakti, The children made me emotional.
Your emotion...
That's all fine,
but why didn't you two get married?
Come here.
You... take that...
so many questions.
Don't hit.
I just asked a question.
Because we didn't
want to become fathers.
See... he's still washing
everyone's clothes.
Ramlal!
Hey Ramlal?
What are you doing?
What are you two doing?
Let go of me, please...
what happened?
Brother Shakti and Anwar
told us everything about your past.
Oh... Everything?
Brother... you would use these
hands to wipe them, isn't it?
Whose?
- Brother, why are you so worried?
- No, I am not worried.
You weren't a beggar.
You were a washerman.
Washerman!?
I am washerman?
Brother... we know everything
about Ramlal and Pogo.
Ramlal?
Who?
Pogo?
Give me this.
Now we'll do all this.
Okay.
You Go!
Okay, okay...
Bye, Ramlal.
Ramlal? Pogo? Washerman?
Raj, you said Veer should
never learn about the truth.
But I never said that
You should turn me into Ramlal.
- We were Mafia, man.
- Yeah, that's right.
But they just pounced
on us... made us swear too...
What else could we do?
You could've said you don't know.
Don't know.
Why don't we know?
We've been together for so long.
And Raj... even we have some honor.
Isn't it brother?
Ohh... that's why you tarnished mine.
Look at my personality,
Do I look like Ramlal from any angle?
Kaali... sorry...
Why are you getting so furious?
Because I know Veer too well.
He won't stay quiet.
He'll do something worse
than the story you just cooked up.
And who's Pogo?
Pogo?
My Sister's name was Pogo?
I don't believe this story.
And my sister left
your brother for money.
- How can this be true?
- lshu, I heard this...
from one of brother's old friend.
His... brother.
It's all true.
What about us now?
Do one thing ...why don't you
two disappear for a few days.
Who knows... maybe out of worry
Ramlal and Pogo melt?
Jenny... they're not some
ice-cream that will melt.
I say that you two should
run away and get married.
No... my sister's done a lot for me.
I cannot hurt her like this.
Even I can't do this
with brother either.
Hold on.
lshu... why didn't my brother and your
sister ever get married to someone else?
Why?
Because... they haven't
forgotten their memories...
and their daily one-night stands.
Veer... you're talking about my sister.
Don't get into the details...
come to the point.
If they did love each other...
then how about we
rekindle that love again?
And patch them up.
What do you say?
- That can solve our problems.
- Exactly.
But how do we patch things up?
How?
Only God knows that.
Patrick, I've heard some new
restaurant has opened up in Panjim.
Yes, the owner is
some woman called Meera.
So go talk to her... and our stuff..
Dude... where's my car.
There...
Where's my car?
Patrick, it had drugs worth millions.
What?
Veer...
I got a superb idea to get
Ramlal and Pogo back together.
What?
We'll hire some goons...
and tell them to chase Pogo.
The hero makes a dynamic entry...
when the villains
chasing the heroine.
Villain's pack up...
and the hero-heroine will patch-up.
What patch up?
What an ancient idea
to rekindle old love, Sid.
Veer... the oldest wine
is the most intoxicating one.
Just say yes... and then see...
I'm sure you'll say...
"What a plan".
- Who will pose as the goon?
- We'll find someone.
That's King's car.
Why are you driving
around in King's car?
I didn't know it was
King's car when I stole it.
- You mean you stole it.
- That too King's car.
Exactly... what will King
do when he finds out?
So change its color...
so I can sell it to someone in Goa.
Mani, you know I will never
help you with stolen stuff.
But the guy whose car you stole...
I've got a score
to settle with him too.
But first we must hide
this car from brother Raj.
- Tavde“.
- Yes, brother.
Hide the car... and
don't tell brother Raj.
You want me to lie to Raj sir?
How about I tell him
you've got a girl. Get lost.
Pinto, come on.
I will never forget
what you two have done for me.
Look, I've said this to brother Raj...
and I'm saying it again to you.
If there's anything I can do for you...
just let me know.
I'll stand
by you head over heels.
- Mani bhai, we do need help.
- Say it!
Okay. You need to
pretend as a goon for us.
Goon?
Brother Raj's love story is stuck.
Huh!
Hero and Heroine will patch-up...
when you trouble
the girl as the villain.
Will you, Mani bhai.?
I can even give up
my life for brother Raj.
Name, place,
animal, thing... just name it.
Say it!
Mani bhai, just handle it.
Everything lies in your hands now.
Don't mess it up.
Look Veer, she's coming.
All the best. - All the best...
careful with the loin-cloth!
Do you want to die? Get out of the way.
- Just one question.
- What?
- ls there a Chintu in your home?
- No.
That's it...
Give me one chance...
and you'll get a Chintu.
What a plan.
And according to the time Raj
will be coming through any minute.
Now you'll say
"What are your intentions".
And I'll say...
Next you'll say
"Don't come any closer".
I'll say...
Then you'll say "Help".
And I'll say "Scream".
But no one will come to save you.
Mani's acting so well.
What a plan.
And then you'll come closer.
Yes.
And hold my hand tightly.
Yes!
That's when you'll realize...
there's actually no one to help...
No one. No one. Correct!
You!
Me.
What are you taking out?
This is cheating.
I don't hit women.
I spare you because you're a woman.
Hit like a woman...
Why are you hitting like a man?
She's letting him have it!
(HE") me!
Where are you going?
Pogo channel turned into WWF.
She smashed me up...
Even these two abandoned me.
Seriously, this is the limit guys.
ls this the way?
- And who comes up with such ideas?
- He does.
Get sister in trouble...
brother will save her...
and those two will fall in love.
That's the limit.
Have you lost your mind, Veer?
- Brother...
- Veer...
And what do you guys think...
by doing this, she ..
That relation is over.
You will gain nothing.
There's no point.
Veer... all this doesn't look good.
Don't be such a fool.
Everything is over.
How can you say that?
Brother...
firstly I am not ready to believe...
that sister left you for money.
And even if she did...
then why didn't
she marry someone else?
You're on the right track...
bombard him with another one.
Why didn't she make anyone
else her life-partner?
Go on. Go on.
And even brother didn't
marry anyone else, right?
Yes, why?
Even you didn't find
anyone else for yourself.
You never even went on a three
night-four day tour with some girl.
Brother Raj... only you
know what's in your heart.
But I've understood
what's in sister's heart.
Regardless of what
happened between you two...
she still hasn't
forgotten her first love.
Veer, deliver the car.
Brother's melting.
Brother, I've another plan.
- Mani bhai...
- Shut up!
I've to attend a meeting.
Wrap up everything
here and come home. Okay thanks.
- Bye.
This car will definitely
break-down before it reaches Panjim.
And like every day,
brother will pass-by.
lshita, something will
definitely happen today.
"Walk with me... in every lifetime."
"Promise me...
you'll come back to me right here."
"We're one soul...
even if we're two bodies."
"Always be mine...
don't ever say goodbye."
"You're my dawn...
and you're my twilight."
"You're the pain...
and you're the comfort."
"There's only one thing
I ever pray for in my mind."
"Always be mine...
don't ever say goodbye."
don't ever say..."
"Both my world lie in your arms."
"My heaven is wherever you are."
"Desire's are burning
in both our hearts."
"l wish my prayers
are never unanswered."
"You're my desire, I am your love."
"You're my poem... l am your music."
"You... You...
You're the one I crave for."
"Become the intoxication in my veins
and keep flowing."
"Repay my love in this way."
"Always be mine...
don't ever say goodbye."
"goodbye."
Veer, superb buddy.
You've done an amazing job.
You completely changed
the look of the car.
Even King can never recognize it.
Veer, what's wrong?
Why are you in a bad mood?
No matter how hard we try...
Pogo and brother's
love story doesn't pick up.
I don't know what to do now.
Veer... l do have an idea.
- No more idea. No, buddy no..
- It's sure shot, please.
At least hear me out. Hear me out.
What if we rekindle their passion?
Passion? How?
There's a new film playing
in Edward's Theatre.
Let's buy corner
seat tickets for them.
They'll watch the film together...
and rekindle their passion.
What film? - 'Tamboo Mein Dhoom-Dham'
(INDIAN C-GRADE FILM).
Come here. Come here.
You and your pervert ideas.
Pinto, wrap the boot.
It's a nice film. I've seen it myself.
Brother, there's a bag in here.
Whose bag is this?
I guess it Mani bhai's.
- This isn't my bag.
- What?
- Then whose bag is it?
- I don't know.
Open it.
Oh God... drugs!
Drugs! This is
definitely King's stuff.
What do we do with it now?
If these drugs get out in the market...
there's no telling how
many will fall prey to it.
Then what do we do it.
Let's burn it.
These drugs were going
to ruin the entire youth.
King... l really enjoyed
burning your stuff.
- I think Mani bhai is drunk.
- Drunk?
He's completely over the top.
- Mani bhai, control.
- What control?
Lose control!
What..
King!
What are you guys burning?
What are you guys burning tell me?
- We're burning the stuff from the car.
- What?
You see... once a month...
we burn all the scrap
from the garage in a bonfire.
Sir... what are you doing here?
- My car's broken down.
- We'll fix it.
- Yeah...
- Ignition.
What?
Why are you laughing?
He's warming his hands
on the ashes of his own stuff.
Shut up, Mani. You'll give us away.
Veer... he's gone.
Fix it quickly.
King... you're looking really smart.
Thank you.
But you would look smarter...
with your father's favorite car.
Did you find the car?
You didn't, right?
King, don't mind... he's drunk.
Mani...
King... was there something in the car?
You didn't find that either, did you?
Hey... show some manners.
He's King.
King... is my Angel.
King...
did you find Kaali?
You didn't find him either.
King... your car's fixed.
Come on.
Mani, what are you doing?
Why do you drink so much?
Veer... Siddhu!
Did Ramlal and Pogo patch up?
They didn't either?
Get out!
We... work for King!
I said get out.
Joshua... that's Kaali!
What's the matter, Veer?
These days you've been
visiting the church quite often.
How did you get so religious?
Yes, brother.
There are only two things
in our life that matters.
Car... and Sans-kar (VALUES).
Nice church, right?
Brother, I'll go get the candles.
Wait here,
sis... I'll go get the candles.
Are you following me?
I came here with Veer.
Where is he?
Raj my boy, you here.
And Joshua told me...
that you're Meera.
Let me introduce myself.
I am King... Charmed.
It's a good thing we met...
I was thinking of
coming over to meet you.
Last night my men came to your shack...
and suddenly Kaali dropped in.
Do you know Kaali?
Because if you do... then tell me.
And I promise you my men
will never trouble you again.
Of course, will finish him.
Do you know Kaali?
I don't know him!
Just once I lay my hand on Kaali...
You know what... I'll pray to
the Lord that you never find Kaali.
Who knows... what will happen...
To him... not you.
- Yeah... Got to go, bro.
- Have a good day.
Oh my....
Veer... you did an amazing job.
You turned a landline
into a smartphone...
and an old piece
of junk into Iron Man.
You turned bat into Batman...
and Spider into Spider' Man.
Oh my...
Blackberry at the bottom...
and Bappi Lahiri on top.
I'll sell this at
the rate of an airplane.
By the way... what's the
rate of airplanes nowadays?
Forget about airplanes
and just go sell this thing.
This is King's car.
- If he finds out...
- Then you'll disappear forever.
Oh... Correct.
Bravo my boy.
Keep this... Lux cozy...
Rupa's underwear.
Underwear.
Oscar bhai,
you look really happy today.
What's the matter?
Bloody raincoat... l could've given
you any amount you had asked for.
Why?
Because my sister just told me...
that she's in love with some boy.
Some boy... who owns a hotel.
Ariel... and Harpic.
Yeah!
Tomorrow I am going to talk to his
family about their marriage.
And if it's fixed...
then I am thinking
of presenting this...
on their wedding.
Hold a second.
Should I present a gift?
Or gift a present?
It's the same thing, Oscar bhai.
A gift is a gift after all...
Wow... you read my heart.
Mani you're just a honey.
Jenny's here, Siddhu.
Jenny?
- Hi, hi...
- What's up, Jenny?
Jenny, you here?
You could've called.
- Guess what?
- What?
I told my brother everything about us.
- And he's agreed to our marriage.
- What?
In fact, he's come here to meet you.
What are you saying, Jenny?
Why are you still standing?
Where is he standing?
- Brother-in-law.
- Siddhu.
Where are you brother-in-law?
Mona Lisa...
Oscar bhai.
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing here?
I'm here to meet
my sister's boyfriend.
And I am here to meet
my girlfriend's brother.
Where is he? Introduce me?
He's the one.
It's him.
- You?
I guess you two know each other
from before.
They know each other too well.
In and out.
Everything that he took
out... he would take in. Right?
In and out.
What are you saying?
Sister, I'll tell you.
This guy's a down-market thief.
Bloody fool... Colgate.. babul.
Thief.
Siddhu, you're a thief.
Well... your brother's a thief too.
- And he's got a shop at the flea-market.
- Brother.
He used to buy all the goods I stole.
Forget your girlfriend's brother...
- Your brother's coming.
- Brother...
Stop him. He'll go berserk.
Brother... brother...
Shakti, please don't...
Did I starve him?
So what was the reason...
Brother, this girl...
This girl is the reason, brother.
Brother, in this era you can ask
any youth like me...
and he'll tell
you that finding love...
has become so expensive and hard.
I mean... if we go watch a film
in the multiplex, that's 800 rupees.
And if you eat a combo
of popcorn and fritters...
then it's 900 rupees.
And after that if your
baby says "Baby, coffee"...
then treating her to coffee
costs almost 1000 rupees.
And all night on your
prepaid card, we do...
"Hello... baby, sweety, love you..."
Then where the 2000 rupees go,
no one knows.
And... gift on her birthday.
Gift on Valentine's Day.
"And baby... we met for
the first time on Friday."
Then every Friday...
there's a weekly anniversary gift.
I mean like... really...
- So many expenses?
- You don't know.
Brother... your era
was completely different.
Your date would mean
eating corncobs and having tea...
and cozying up behind stones.
But the girls these days
are very high maintenance.
Ask us...
We've to pay weekly at multiplexes,
coffee shops...
and malls to prove our love.
It is not that easy.
It's bloody extortion.
Siddhu...
Relax, Siddhu...
or you'll blow a nerve.
Wait, I'll handle him now.
Siddhu .. we didn't know you were
going through so many troubles.
It's so expensive.
Shakti, the poor boy's
stuck between love and expenses.
- Puraskar bhai..
- Oscar bhai.
It's the same thing.
You're an award after all.
- Siddhu's a nice guy.
- Yeah.
For me, Siddhu is just like Veer.
Oscar bhai, he's my brother.
We're a descent family.
No criminal records.
Forget that,
he loves your sister so much.
He's well to do.
The café, garage, property...
It will all belong
to these two after us.
- Please, say yes.
- But how can I say yes.
Why not?
You two are already
a match made in heaven.
Us?
You two are sailing in the same boat.
Don't feel embarrassed.
Feel proud of him.
But...
- Brother, please say yes.
- Come on, say yes.
Okay... l agree to this marriage...
Jackie Shroff lookalike.
But I have a condition.
- ls someone going to ask what?
- What?
The marriage takes
place in a church.
What are you saying?
Everyone agreed to Siddhu
and Jenny's marriage.
That's great news.
Their family said yes...
l wonder when will
our family say yes.
Don't worry,
Veer... they will say yes.
Tell Siddhu we want a party.
Let's all meet and celebrate.
What say?
- Yeah, okay. Cool.
- Bye.
I told you... not to keep
any kind of relation with them.
Sis...
Sis... you've a problem
with that family. Not me.
And you're not telling
me what that problem is either.
I don't understand
why you're doing this, sis.
After mom and dad passed away...
I've always fulfilled
all your wishes and wants.
And never asked why.
I even let you take
your own decisions.
And never asked why.
So today, for the first time, when
I am stopping you from something...
can't you do this much for me?
Fine, sis... I'll do everything you say.
I'll never ask anything, I promise.
But if not Veer...
then there won't be
anyone else in my life.
lshita...
Call Veer home tomorrow.
- I want to talk to him.
- You mean...
Ask him to come alone.
Thank you, Pogo... Ma'am.
Sorry...!
Brother will be really
happy to know that you said yes.
But now you must accept
one of my condition!
Done.
I mean... whatever it is, I agree.
You can say it for formality,
but done.
After the marriage,
you must live here.
If you want to be with lshita...
you must leave your brother.
Sis... what are you saying?
Are you joking?
lshu... this is a big issue.
Meera's asking me
to leave my brother.
See, I really love you...
but he isn't just my brother.
He's my father,
mother, friend... everything.
All his life he has only
cared about my happiness.
And she wants...
Sorry madam... you might
own a restaurant.
But this is not some
home-delivery or take-away.
lshita, I am sorry.
But nothing is more
important than a brother.
Not even you.
Veer!
You're leaving her
for that brother of yours.
He isn't even your blood brother.
Your dad picked him
up from the streets.
lshita...
You don't believe me.
Ask him yourself.
Enough!
Where were you Veer?
I've been asking around for you.
Come, let's eat...
What happened?
- I wanted to ask you something.
- Ask. Why are you standing like that?
ls there something you've ever hidden
from me?
What could I ever hide from you?
No! There's nothing
I have hidden from you.
You're not my blood brother.
- Who told you that?
- lshita's sister.
Why are you quiet?
Just tell me, you have my swear.
It's true that I am not
your blood brother.
It's a different thing that
I love you more than a blood brother.
And it's true that
I hid this fact from you.
It's a different thing...
I didn't want to lose you.
lshita's sister has a
condition for our marriage.
That I should leave you.
So... what did you say?
Get lost...
I left lshita, brother.
Brother... I'll find someone else.
But first I'll make sure that
she doesn't have an elder sister.
Don't forget to check.
Who knows...
I might have an affair...
with every beautiful
girl's elder sister.
You bluntly said no?
Do you really love me so much?
Don't just stand there,
come here.
What did you want to do?
You wanted to separate two brothers.
Did it pain that much?
The very thought of separating
from your kin was painful.
Think about what I went
though... when you killed my dad.
- Did you think about it..
- I didn't kill your dad.
- You're lying.
- It's true!
It's true! Look into my eyes.
I swear on my brother that
I didn't kill your father.
Look into my eyes Meera...
this is the truth.
We were the ones who were betrayed.
Us.
And if you still don't believe me,
then take this...
and end this matter right now.
Shoot, Meera. Shoot.
I won't survive from
this close, Meera.
Shoot!
Shoot!.
"Why do they hold back
the love in your heart?"
"Boundaries."
"Why do they bring
a distance in love?"
"Boundaries."
"Our dreams were delicate like glass."
"They shattered as
soon as we touched them."
"The one whose company
I prayed for..."
"that companion separated."
"Dying isn't right..."
"but living isn't an option either."
"Boundaries."
"Boundaries"
Malik sir was the
one who betrayed them.
Whatever Kaali said is true.
Raghav, why didn't
you tell me this before?
I couldn't
go against Malik sir.
And I didn't want
a daughter to find out...
what her father has done.
You don't know what you've done.
You love your brother a lot,
don't you?
Yes!
And my lshita too.
Then marry her and stay here.
With your brother.
What?
You mean... l won't die a bachelor.
I'll get married too.
- I'll go on a honeymoon too.
- Veer.
I mean... would you like some tea.
You must have tea.
I suggest that you have
breakfast instead, Pogo.
lshita, come.
We'll go to the kitchen and make tea.
Come...
Brother, don't just stand there...
Pogo's come home for the first time.
Show her the garage,
the house, the sofa...
Come on, brother.
Nice house.
It's new.
Thank you.
That's... our garage.
We modify car...
Designing... styling...
Fiber... the works...
You always loved cars.
That's Anwar and Shakti.
Remember?
Now they run a café.
Still multi-talented I guess.
Raghav told me the truth.
That's true.
- You haven't changed at all.
- Except for a little beard.
Actually... you haven't changed either.
- Maybe I've put on a little weight.
- Yes, a little...
l...l didn't mean that.
You... do look fine, same like before.
Really?
" No!
Only a little.
I am sorry.
It's been 15 years Kaali.
15 years...
4 months...
10 days!
The rest of the garage's ours too.
Engineering department... Auto CAD...
The whole...
I am so sorry!
I thought what I saw was the truth.
I didn't give you a chance to explain.
I didn't believe you.
I wanted to tell you, Meera.
But you were already gone. And...
I came here.
But you know what...
Let's forget all this now.
We... we don't need to look back now.
But it was entirely my fault.
I can't...
It wasn't your fault... nor mine.
The circumstances were to be blamed.
- Meera, I...
- I.
Good morning, Raj bhai.
Here comes the wedding
days... Kurkure and Lays (WAFERS).
Come with me...
The wedding procession is coming.
- Raj bhai, let's go.
- Where?
To make the wedding guest list.
If I make one, only thieves
and criminals will come.
And they'll even steal the cutlery.
Raj bhai... who is she?
- Your wife?
- No..
No no, you're not married yet.
- Your girlfriend.
- No...
No... you don't have a girlfriend either.
What?
After seeing the wedding procession. Are you
dreaming of Becoming a groom as well.
- What are you saying? What are you doing?
- Speak up naughty fellow.
Come on, let's go and talk there.
Okay.
By the way, I am Oscar.
What do I call her?
Can I call her sister-in-law?
"Walk with me... in every lifetime."
"Promise me...
you'll come back to me right here."
"We're one soul...
even if we're two bodies."
"Always be mine...
don't ever say goodbye."
Pogo, thank you.
Now even I can get
married because of you.
I did nothing.
When there's love... then
you should get married.
Then why didn't you get married yet.
There's a reason, I can't tell you.
But can I tell you something?
When I came here with
Siddhu to book this place...
l got a wonderful news.
Even if you hold two weddings here,
the price of the hall is still same.
And... the expenses for decorator
and caterer is also the same.
Very enticing.
But tell me one thing...
Does my face tell you I am a miser?
No.
That's not it.
But there has to be some excuse...
to take things forward.
Look.
They look so happy.
Yes, they are.
Soon lshita and Veer
will get married too.
You will miss lshita a lot.
A lot.
Actually you can come
home everyday to meet lshita.
In fact, I can even
pick you up from the shack.
You can have dinner with us.
Nowadays I even cook well.
- Really?
- Really.
So taxi, catering,
escort service... whatever.
Wow!
But... pickup and drop every day.
I must think of another
way to meet lshita every day.
Actually, I do have a way.
What?
Can you meet me for
five minutes tomorrow?
Huh?
I'll think about it.
This is my car.
Open the boot!
Joshua... who is the man here,
claiming this car to be his car?
You.
You only said it...
Go and bring that guy.
Yes, sir.
Whiter than white...
that's Oscar family.
Where are you taking me?
Is there less salt in the food.
Hail Mother Mary.
When asked,
He said that he owns the car.
Yeah...
When the dog's about the die...
the Thakur's manager says,
"Thakur's dead".
That's nothing original.
It's a dialogue from
Karan-Arjun (BOLLYWOOD FILM).
Maybe you don't know who I am.
I am King. King.
So do you want me to make your
adhaar card, son of burger king.
This car...
Don't even dream about this car.
I won't sell it at any cost.
And anyway, Oscar never
deals with the likes of you.
Have your food and leave quietly.
Forgive me... it's not my fault.
Mani stole this car
and brought it to me.
When the dog's about the die...
the neighboring puppy
eyes his young widow.
How nice, sir...
Neighboring puppy...
young widow.
What a message.
Where's everyone?
Hello... one, two, three, four...
Widow... puppy..-
Everyone's right here, Mani.
Just that... my right and your
left indicator is switched on, son.
Mani... there were drugs
worth millions in the boot!
Veer found those packets.
I don't know what he did with it.
Ask him and he'll tell you.
Hello.
Get Veer!
What's all this, King?
Why bring me here like this?
When the dog's about the die...
Joshua, I am out of stock.
Have you got anything?
- I have with a cat.
- Shut up!
Mani bhai. Oscar bhai, why are you both
looking in the opposite directions?
Are you angry with each other?
No, they were being stiff with me.
So... l stiffened their neck.
King, you're crossing your limits.
I am.
Because back in college...
Seema and Rekha didn't
let me cross my limits.
It happens with everyone, King.
Don't get emotional.
What did you do with my drugs, Veer?
Whatever I did,
you were involved in it too?
Meaning?
Your drugs were burning
in the same bonfire...
where you were keeping
your hands warm.
I kept asking you
"Was there something in the car".
Hello, One, two, three, four...
Are you crazy?
You burned away drugs worth millions.
Veer. Veer.
Kaali!
We know the truth, sis.
Brother told us everything.
Don't worry.
Yeah... you were right
and brother was wrong.
You left him because...
brother turned from washer man Ramlal
into Kaali for money.
And you didn't want his
bad influence on my upbringing.
So you...
Pogo, please rest. Would
you like some juice? I'll go get it.
Have an apple too.
Come lshu come.
- Brother..
- Yeah... got it.
Why didn't you tell them the truth?
Because we shouldn't
tell them in the first place.
What's the point, Meera?
The enmity between our dads...
Killing each other... Why?
Actually,
we should all start afresh.
And no one needs to look back.
But why did you prove yourself wrong,
and me right?
You see...
In big countries...
these small things often happen...
Senorita.
"It's the night to celebrate."
"Sway to the beat,
O my tormentor."
"Your mischief lights up the place."
"You went crazy, and I got attitude."
"Let the world be jealous."
"And the beloved dances
all night with her sweetheart."
"Life is like a saga."
"The style of big-hearted people."
"When I grab the opportunity."
"The way to live freely."
"Learn this method from us."
"We have all the fun in a moment."
"Come and have fun with us."
"Or just stay away
and watch us have fun."